{
    "id": "5b2c2ddef0664cf184a59b9c73126091",
    "title": "Exclamations | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "............................... cold it is!",
            "description": "We use 'how' before an adjective and 'what' before an adjective + noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "What",
                "Such"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9db18b745717455497067cd6b042c0b7"
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................. lovely weather!",
            "description": "We use 'how' before an adjective and 'what' before an adjective + noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e6db6fb8bfd748b19ecb38bd831b146c"
        },
        {
            "question": "How beautifully ..............................!",
            "description": "Note the pattern: how + adjective/adverb + subject + verb",
            "answers": [
                "dances she",
                "does she dance",
                "she dances"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7b30a2e2d32b4bb2a4d8b6859e432ebc"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................ pleasant surprise!",
            "description": "We use 'What a/an' before adjective + singular countable noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How",
                "What a"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0a30ca347a8a4a8bae79ff61b6703850"
        },
        {
            "question": "What a beautiful smile ................................!",
            "description": "In exclamations the subject goes before the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "your daughter has",
                "has your daughter",
                "does your sister have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f02046e0c625425f97c6d73408d5c8fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "You talk ............................. rubbish!",
            "description": "'Such' is used before an uncountable noun. 'Such a' is used before a countable noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7d13001d1aa8431e9de1a443245140ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is .................................. beautiful!",
            "description": "So is used before an adjective. Such is used before a noun or adjective + noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3e018ef7d9294d51aeecd9aff8941fca"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is .............................. kind woman!",
            "description": "Use such a before a singular countable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7b5b1b4336864e9f90156310acf28710"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................... shameful defeat!",
            "description": "Use 'what a' before a singular noun or adjective + singular noun.",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "What a",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "84bbfedbb53545cb8124ef2d3b9704f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ............................. clever boy!",
            "description": "Use 'such a' before adjective + singular countable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "05565105e20d45578417e72d87ef3206"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. beautiful flowers!",
            "description": "Use 'what' before adjective + noun.",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9f7f33f63af3417d93a90fec0d099acf"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ big city Tokyo is!",
            "description": "We use 'what a' before adjective + singular countable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "What a",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "89478f2bc0444053812fa7eaf06fa639"
        }
    ]
}